{"data":[{"question":"He doesn't much like the work, but he enjoyed the relationships with the other workers.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"much","b":"but","c":"enjoyed","d":"with","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Enjoyed-> enjoys","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"After getting her six-year-old daughter ready and driving her to the school, she starts on the housework.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"getting","b":"six-year-old","c":"driving","d":"the school","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- The school-> school","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"She finds housework bored and doesn't like to stay at home all day.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"finds","b":"bored","c":"doesn't","d":"to stay","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Bored-> boring","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"A artist went to a beautiful part of the country for a holiday, and stayed with a farmer.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"A","b":"to","c":"beautiful","d":"for","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- A-> an","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"The artist was very pleased and thanked the farmer for saying so kind things about the paintings.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"pleased","b":"saying","c":"so","d":"about","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- So-> such","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Several members of his family did a great deal to encourage him in the field of scientific.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Several","b":"to encourage","c":"in","d":"scientific","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Scientific-> science","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"While he dealt with the deaf and investigating the science of acoustics, his studies eventually led to the invention of the multiple telegraph and his greatest invention - the telephone.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"dealt","b":"investigating","c":"eventually","d":"invention","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Investigating-> investigated","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Along in jogging and swimming, cycling is one of the best all-round forms of exercise.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"in","b":"cycling","c":"one","d":"of","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- In-> with","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"It can help to increase your strong and energy, giving you more efficient muscles and a stronger heart.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to increase","b":"strong","c":"giving","d":"stronger","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Strong-> strength","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Doing too much too quickly can damage muscles that aren't used to work.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Doing","b":"quickly","c":"aren't","d":"to work","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- To work-> working","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"}]}